<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Darlene Zouras - Comfy Coding v2</title>
    <description>Just another minimalist Jekyll theme that focuses on technical writing.</description>
    <link>http://darzouras.me/blog/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://darzouras.me/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 17:19:39 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 17:19:39 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back to the Blog</title>
        <description>&lt;h3 id=&quot;after-some-time-away-from-writing-its-time-to-get-back-at-it&quot;&gt;After some time away from writing, it’s time to get back at it.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For a year I kept up a Wordpress blog at ComfyCoding.com, only to find myself neglecting it some when school and work started to become a little too much to juggle. That blog was a great way to document what I have learned and found during my first year coding. I hoped that it could become a learning tool for others- that they could learn from my struggles! I want to continue to document my experience as a learner in order to reflect as well as share how I’ve solved the problems I’ve encountered!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since fall classes have just wrapped up, there’s not necessarily much to report on at the moment. I took Web Development and Databases last term, and I’ll be starting Operating Systems and Software Development I in January. Until then the holidays have me set up for a pretty easy work schedule and I would love to dig into a personal project, or learn something new entirely. Right now I’m leaning towards working with Electron, which means that I might have the chance to work through some new JS libraries! Or I’ll keep working with the few that I’ve learned this past term. I could change gears completely and build something in the first language I’ve ever learned, Python! I’d love to learn how to build something using Python and Django now that I’ve got database basics under my belt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, I will be able to consider all of this after I can successfully get this blog up and running on Github!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://darzouras.me/blog/2016/back-to-the-blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://darzouras.me/blog/2016/back-to-the-blog/</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
